itravel2000.com 2015-06-24

# Privacy Policy - Keeping your data safe - Itravel2000

(Updated for the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, Part 1, 01 Jan, 2006). 

Prices, Purchasing and Privacy   
Your "Peace of Mind" is our Top Priority.

At itravel2000, providing a private and secure purchase environment is our top priority.

We recognize the importance of ensuring your privacy and protecting your purchases.

  * We guarantee that your purchase is safe and secure. 
  * We guarantee that your privacy will be respected. 

itravel2000 strives to maintain the highest industry standards for online privacy and security. 

Purchase Policy  
While we are confident that transactions on our site are secure, we recognize that you may have concerns about purchasing travel online. To ensure that every transaction is safe, itravel2000 offers online purchasing options only on servers that have been verified as secure and use the most advanced encryption technology, making it virtually impossible for your credit-card information to be used fraudulently online. 

Remember, your piece of mind is our top priority. At itravel2000 you always have the option of calling one of our travel experts to complete your purchase.

Privacy Policy  
We Respect Your Privacy. Protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your Personally Identifying Information has always been fundamental to the way we do business with you at itravel2000, whether over the Internet, on the telephone or in person at our office. 

Trade-marks and Copyrights  
Certain names, words, titles, phrases, logos, icons, graphics or designs or other content in the pages of the Site are trade names or trade-marks owned by 8635919 CANADA INC. (dba itravel2000) or its subsidiaries, or trade names or trade-marks licensed to them. 

Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, trade-marks owned by 8635919 CANADA INC. (dba itravel2000) include the following: ITRAVEL2000, ITRAVELCASH, TRAVELCASH, REDMAN GROUP, and REDEMPTION MANAGEMENT GROUP, and other trade-marks composed of "ITRAVEL2000". 

These trade-marks are used by 8635919 CANADA INC. (dba itravel2000) and/or subsidiaries under license. Some trade-marks are distinguished from one another and accompanied, at first-time use, with the appropriate trade-mark symbol: ®/™/*. These symbols are keyed to their respective legend which describes the owner or licensee of the trade-mark: ® Registered trade-mark of 8635919 CANADA INC. (dba itravel2000)./™ Trade-mark of 8635919 CANADA INC. (dba itravel2000)./* 8635919 CANADA INC. (dba itravel2000), licensee of trade-mark. 

The display of trade-marks and trade names on pages at the Site does not imply that a licensee of any kind has been granted to anyone else. The Information is for your personal use only. Any unauthorized downloading, re-transmission, or other copying or modification of trade-marks and/or the contents of the Site may be a violation of any federal or other law that may apply to trade-marks and/or copyrights and could subject the copier to legal action. The Information is protected under the copyright laws of Canada and other countries. Unless otherwise specified, no one has permission to copy, redistribute, reproduce, republish, store in any medium, re-transmit, modify or make public or commercial use of, in any form, the Information. 

What is Personally Identifying Information?  
"Personally identifying information" ("PII") is information that can be explicitly used to identify and/or contact you as an individual. This includes information like your real name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, etc. Information that, by itself, cannot be explicitly linked with your "real" identity is not considered personally identifying. Examples of this are favourite or bookmarked Web sites, or your preferences with respect to how you wish to see a given page or site set up according to the selections you choose. 

Use of Personally Identifying Information  
itravel2000 takes your privacy seriously and will not share your Personally identifying information without your consent. If you choose to use one of the features below, your PII will be used as follows: 

Cookies  
We use cookies and other technologies to let us know when you're a repeat visitor to our site (and _only_ our site) so that we may be able to better offer you a personalized experience. We use this information to provide the services you request, including the display of personalized content and advertising. This information is kept in strict confidence and is used only for these purposes, as covered within the General Privacy Policy. 

Reservations and Purchases  
When you make a reservation or purchase online with itravel2000, we will share information about you and your purchase with the applicable airline, hotel, car-rental agency, tour operator or other travel suppliers. We will only provide the necessary information to ensure your travel arrangements are confirmed with these travel suppliers. The travel suppliers will use your credit-card information to process your ticket or reservation.

Opting-in to Receive Our Newsletter  
By opting in to receive our newsletter, you are eligible to win monthly travel prizes. You may opt out of the newsletter by using the unsubscribe link on the newsletter when you receive it or by clicking here unsubscribe. If you choose to opt out of receiving the newsletter your email address will be deleted from our database and you will no longer receive it. This also means that you will no longer be eligible to win monthly travel prizes. 

Communicating With You  
If you are a member, contest entrant, or purchaser, we will occasionally use your e-mail address or PII to contact you for the purpose of:

  * Reservation confirmations 
  * Important updates about your travel plans 
  * Newsletters 
  * Notifications of travel specials. 

We hope you find this information informative.

Third-Party Sites  
Remember, itravel2000 will not disclose or sell any of your personal information, including your name, address, credit-card number, shopping, or transaction history to any third party without your permission. Please be aware that our site contains links to other sites and that the privacy practices of other sites may differ from those of itravel2000. In certain situations, you may link to another site within an itravel2000 frame that shows an itravel2000 URL. In these cases itravel2000 makes all reasonable efforts to confirm the security and privacy practices of these sites, but despite the itravel2000 frame and URL, each site is responsible for its own privacy practices. 

Other Privacy Policy Considerations  
During the course of subscribing to itravel2000 services or purchasing travel products through itravel2000 the information collected will be limited to PII necessary for the stated purpose. Further, itravel2000 will provide you access to your PII within the required timeframe, upon written request, in order that you may review your PII for accuracy and completeness. itravel2000 will amend any PII found to be incorrect or deficient. 

How to Contact Us  
If you have additional questions or concerns, please e-mail us at [youtravel@itravel2000.com](mailto:youtravel@itravel2000.com). We read every customer e-mail and will respond as soon as possible. 

For specific inquiries or concerns relating to itravel2000's security and privacy policies and practices, you can contact our Privacy Officer at [privacy@itravel2000.com](mailto:privacy@itravel2000.com). 

Alternately, feel free to call or write:

itravel2000.com  
1004 Middlegate Rd. Suite 3000. Mississauga, Ontario, L4Y 1M4

General: 416-695-9999   
Facsimile: 905.238.6177   
Reservations: 416-695-9999   
Toll Free: 1.866.WOW.DEAL (969.3325)
